Let's first move towards the shares whose
name is Surf Limited. Today,
you are
seeing a decline of 1.4 i.e. almost 33 points in Surf Limited. If we
talk about which company, then Surf
Limited is seen to be a very strong company financially
and at the same time, the
company has given very good returns in the last 5 minutes.
Right now you can see these companies at a very
discounted rate price, due to which
you can add on your positions here keeping in mind the stop loss of ₹2000.
Regarding the net shell, whose name is ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company Limited.
Yes, after the listing of ICICI Lombard, the
company has given 70% returns to its investors so far, that is,
if you had done HD in any bank in 2017
or had
invested in ICICI Lombard of this
amount, then
you are getting to see very good returns from ICICI Lombard.
This
company has also maintained the performance of consistency.  If you see this,
you can invest here too. Let's talk
about the company called
Infosys India Limited (naukri.com). Yes,
friends, if we talk about
nahin.com, then
this company is taking full advantage of all the startups you see online right now. If we
talk about Infosys, then today
you are seeing a decline of one to one and a quarter percent in this company as well.
If you look at the returns of this company for maximum years, then
we have seen very good returns already in Infosys. So,
if you
want to invest in Infotech, then
you can definitely invest in these shares as well.
You are also getting to see this stock at a very discounted price right now. Let's
talk
about the market leader company called
Relaxo Footwear. There was
no major decline in Footwear Limited,
but again, you can see the shares of Relaxo Footwear Limited
trading around its support.
Yes
friends, the support of ₹1000
is very important in Relaxo Footwear, but if you
look at the performance of Relaxo Footwear, then
this company has given a very good performance to
its investors, along with this,
we get to see a very good demand for the products of this company in the market,
so if you want to invest in this company, then
you can definitely add Relaxo Foodwares to your
portfolio and move on. Let's
talk about the last stock
whose name is Policy India
Limited. Today,
you are seeing almost a rise of 1 percent and a fall of 1 percent in Policy India Limited,
but if we talk about Policy India
Limited, then this company has given a great return of
almost 300%
to its investors since its listing, so
these five best
market leader stocks that I have suggested to you are available to you at a
very discounted price, at a
very cheap price, so
already if you have
invested, then
these shares are in loss here.  There are no sellers here,
you can hold your position here
but if you want to create a fresh position
then in every fall you can add one or two
shares to your portfolio.
Hope you
liked the video and the update. If you liked the video and the
update then do not forget to like and share it. There will be
some important update in the next video, till then
stay updated.